So, we're going to do Squat Jumps next.
And, we're going to use our resistance bands to keep ourselves steady and balanced using each other.
Also, strengthening the arms while doing it.
So, I'm going to demonstrate.
Grace and I are going to demonstrate how to do Squat Jumps using your resistance bands.
So, our arms are nice and straight and out.
Our elbows are locked.
And, what we're going to do.
We're going to squat down, hold it and jump up.
Squat and jump.
Squat, jump.
Be sure to breathe.
You really get deep on that squat.
Feel it in the legs.
Keep your arms up.
You keep your arms nice and out, so they get strengthened this really gives you a cardiovascular exercise because of the jump.
And, it also strengthens the legs like crazy.
Also, the arms are nice and strong and getting stronger from holding them out with resistance.
So, those are squat jumps.